We are here, the team at the Amanda Steele Show for our group chat topic of the week.
Have you ever dated, married, had kids with a liar?
Let's go to the phone line.
I dated this dude for about a year and a half and he was such a compulsive liar.
I got so bad where I would even follow him around,
even if it was as simple as going to the grocery store.
Because this man would tell me that he was going over to his mother's house
and end up somewhere totally different.
I promise I will never date another liar again.
I think the weird part for me is we keep hearing stories about people who like,
they acknowledge that this person is a liar, but they still stay.
And they become like wrapped up in it.
Yeah, I can't believe that she was stalking this guy now based off his life.
You can't?
That's like...
You never stalked nobody.
I feel like I've heard...
No, I've never stalked anybody.
I have never rolled past a house or two.
That's not stalking.
Just about.
Yes, it is.
That's not stalking.
What are you talking about?
I remember being in a car with one of my homegirls and they like were going to go stalk somebody.
And I found out that that's what we were about to do.
And I said, let me out.
I don't want to be a part of this.
He said, okay, Trey.
Yes.
Let me out.
I don't want to be a part of this.
That was peak reference.
Peak reference.
We are, we are, we are, we are.